costraden.com 2018-09-22

# Privacy Notice : Women Fashion | Shop Women's and Women's Wear

http://www.costraden.com GROUP. is committed to respecting your privacy and recognizes your need to protect the personally identifiable information that you share with us on this website. As you may know, when you visit sites on the internet, the owner of the site has the ability to collect information about you, from your name and address to your shopping preferences. Our goal is to adhere to the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy and comply with all applicable laws that are designed to protect your privacy.

POLICY UPDATES

http://www.costraden.com may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Whenever we make a change, we will post the updated policy on this page. That way users can stay informed of our information collection polices. Accordingly, we recommend that you consult this page frequently so that you are aware of our updated policies.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

"Personal Information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on this website, we may transfer that information within http://www.costraden.com or to http://www.costraden.com's third-party service providers.

WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION

http://www.costraden.com is able to collect Personal Information from when you use this website. This can be done only when you voluntarily submit such information on our site. For example, when you make a purchase a product from our site, register for a http://www.costraden.com member account, when you subscribe to an email newsletter, when you order our catalogue, when you participate in our surveys and when you register for contests, sweepstakes, and other promotional opportunities provided by http://www.costraden.com, you are supplying us with your Personal Information. We use such information to display content and products that we think may be of interest to you, to personalize your online experience and to improve the quality of the content that we provide to you on the site. From time to time we may share such information with our business partners, who might also wish to offer their products or services to you. Whenever we request that you provide us Personal Information, we will give you the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving future communications from us or others. By providing such Personal Information to http://www.costraden.com, you agree that, unless you expressly opt out of receiving such information, we may use your Personal Information to fulfill the activity you signed up for, such as purchasing a product, notifying sweepstakes winners or sending you our catalogue, and contacting you with updates regarding the site. Whether or not you provide such information is completely your own choice. You are not obligated to answer any question that is presented to you. Please note that if you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you. http://www.costraden.com does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent. http://www.costraden.com may also disclose your Personal Information when required by law or court order.

If you have provided Personal Information but later you object to the use that is being made of that information (for example, you no longer wish to receive promotional or marketing information about products, services, and offerings from http://www.costraden.com or any third parties) you can ask that we stop making use of that information. You can do this by canceling your http://www.costraden.com member account. Simply send an email message to us and be sure to indicate "UNSUBSCRIBE" in the subject line. Your request will be processed as soon as possible. Please bear in mind that cancellation of your member account will result in you not being able to continue to access the relevant services, offers or content.

PROTECTING CHILDREN

We take special care to protect the safety and privacy of children. Our site is a general audience site. Nevertheless, we do not permit children under age 13 to register on our site for any product or service. We do not collect or solicit personal information about users under age 13. Children under age 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any personal information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in your children's online activities and use parental control or other internet filtering technology to supervise your children's access to the internet.

COOKIES

Our site uses "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from an internet server and stored in your computer. Generally, we use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our products and services to suit your personal interests, estimate our audience size, allow us to better understand how users use the site, to track your status in our promotions, contests and sweepstakes, and/or to analyze your visiting patterns. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it or to block cookies.

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. These tracking technologies allow us to improve our web site and your web site experience. We may also use these tracking technologies to analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.

SECURITY

We understand the utmost importance of protecting the security of your Personal Information that you share with us. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our site, and you do so at your own risk.

LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES

This site may contain links and references to sites and organizations operated and maintained by third parties. http://www.costraden.com has no control whatsoever over such third parties or their internet sites or their products or services. The privacy policies for such linked sites or products or services may be different from our Privacy Policy. You should always read the privacy policy for a linked site or organization before disclosing any personal information on such site or in exchange for any product or service.

CALIFORNIA NOTICE OF INFORMATION - SHARING DISCLOSURE

http://www.costraden.com's Privacy Policy is to share personal information only with the owner's informed consent. With your consent, from time-to-time, http://www.costraden.com may provide its business partners with contact details for direct marketing purposes of relevant services, products, and programs. If you no longer wish your information to be shared, please let us know. If you have further inquires regarding http://www.costraden.com's Information Sharing Practices, please let us know.
